Guide to the McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File, 1948-1991
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Administration Series (ADM), 22 Boxes
  - ADM 0. Corporate Organization and Administration
    - McGraw-Hill Department of Economics: Annual Survey of Overseas Operations of U.S. Industrial Companies
      - 0:2-7 General Management, N.E.C. (Box 8)
        - 0:2-7.14 Matrix Management
          (Matrices find application in many management and marketing techniques; for example, in marketing planning, in executive development, in cost determination, in conglomerate enterprises, in organizational designs, in corporate long-range planning. For that reason, each subject heading relative to a specific topic must be searched for explicit matrix material. For library reference purposes it is suggested that this heading be used to house duplicates of articles, etc., covering these special uses of matrices.)
        - 0:2-7.15 Murphy's Laws, Pareto's Principle and Other Similar Dicta
          See also: ADM 0:2-7.19, Peter/Paul Principles
        - [OD (Organizational Development)--see: ADM 0:1-2, Organizational Development - OD]
        - 0:2-7.16 Operational Research
        - 0:2-7.17 Overseas Management Concepts and Styles
          See also: IOP 5:6, International - Comparative - Management: Role, Problems and Techniques of the International Manager, N.E.C., and all subsections
        - [Paperwork Control--see: ADM 0:2-7.4.1, Paperwork Control]
        - 0:2-7.18 Participative Management
          See also: ADM 0:2-1.8, Worker Participation on BODs
        - [PERT--see: ADM 0:2-7.4.2, Planning Methods - PERT, CPM, RAMPS, etc.]
        - 0:2-7.19 Peter/Paul Principles
          See also: ADM 0:2-7.15, Murphy's Laws, Pareto's Principle and Other Similar Dicta
        - [Planning Methods--see: ADM 0:2-7.4.2, Planning Methods - PERT, CPM, RAMPS, etc.]
        - [RAMPS--see: ADM 0:2-7.4.2, Planning Methods - PERT, CPM, RAMPS, etc.]
        - [Results-Oriented Management--see: ADM 0:2-7.1, Accountability]
        - 0:2-7.20 Secretaries
          See also: ADM 0:2-3, Corporate Secretaries
        - 0:2-7.21 Situational Theory
        - [Specialists vs. Generalists--see: ADM 0:2-7.13.4, Specialists vs. Generalists]
        - 0:2-7.22 Spouses
        - 0:2-7.23 Supervisor's Job
        - 0:2-7.24 Systems Theory in Management (Box 14)
          See also: ADM 0:2-7.6, Decision-Making
        - 0:2-7.25 Task Force Management
        - [Technical Management--see: ADM 0:2-7.13.5, Technical Management]
        - 0:2-7.26 Theories X, Y and Z
          See also: ADM 0:2-7.18, Participative Management
        - [Time Conservation--see: ADM 0:2-7.4.3, Time Conservation; SAL 5:6-5, Sales, Management and Control of Time]
        - 0:2-7.27 Tomorrow's Management
        - 0:2-7.28 Women in Management
          See also: MKT 40:3-1.2, Women in Marketing; MKT 40:3-2.2, Women in Communications; SAL 5:4, Women in Selling
      - [Marketing Management: all aspects except Sales--see: MKT 40, MARKETING/COMMUNICATIONS ADMINISTRATION, all subsections; for Sales Management, see SAL 10, SALES MANAGEMENT, all subsections]
      - 0:2-8 Personnel Management and Relations
        - 0:2-8.1 Personnel Management/Department Structure/Staffing, N.E.C.
        - 0:2-8.2 Affirmative Action/EEO/Discrimination
        - 0:2-8.3 Attitude Surveys
        - [Career Pathing--see: ADM 0:2-8.21.6, Career Advancement, Pathing and Planning]
        - 0:2-8.4 Compensation: Executive/Management; Salary Administration Concepts, Planning, Principles, Programs and Commentary, N.E.C.
        - 0:2-8.4 Compensation: Executive/Management; Salary Administration Concepts, Planning, Principles, Programs and Commentary, N.E.C. (Box 15)
          See also: ADV 5:10-9, Advertising Agencies, Salaries; MKT 40:1-8, Marketing Communications Functions, Compensation; SAL 20:1, Compensation, Sales Executives and Managers; SAL 20:3 and 20:3-1, Compensation, Salespersons
          - 0:2-8.4.1 Compensation: Selected, Regularly-Published studies
            - 0:2-8.4.1.1 AMS (Administrative Management Society): Guide to Management Compensation (annual)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.2 Administrative Management (now, Office Administration and Automation): Administrative Managers' Compensation (biennial)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.3 Business Week: Annual Survey of Executive Compensation
            - 0:2-8.4.1.4 The Conference Board: Top Executive Compensation (biennial)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.5 The Dartnell Corporation: Executive Compensation (biennial)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.6 Financial Executive: Executive Compensation During ... (year) (biennial)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.7 Forbes: Who Gets the Most Pay (annual)
            - 0:2-8.4.1.8 Inc.: The Inc. Annual Compensation Survey
            - 0:2-8.4.1.9 The Wharton Annual: The Hay Report on Executive Compensation
          - 0:2-8.4.2 Cafeteria (flexible approach to compensation)
          - 0:2-8.4.3 Deferred Compensation
          - 0:2-8.4.4 Perquisites (PERKS); includes information on sabbaticals.
          - 0:2-8.4.5 Stock Options/Purchase Plans; includes information on performance shares
        - 0:2-8.5 Fringe Benefits
        - 0:2-8.6 Group Travel Restrictions
        - 0:2-8.7 Health: Alcoholism, Drugs, Stress, Burn-Out, etc.; includes information on company medical departments
        - 0:2-8.8 Human Resource Management/Manpower Planning
        - 0:2-8.9 Interviewing
          See also: ADM 0:2-8.21.13.3, Termination; SAL 35:1-2, Sales, Interviewing
        - [Job Descriptions--see: ADM 0:2-8.15, Position Descriptions/Job Posting, and reference there]
        - 0:2-8.10 Job Enrichment
        - 0:2-8.11 Lie Detectors in Employment
        - [Medical Departments--see: ADM 0:2-8.7, Health]
        - 0:2-8.12 Motivating Employees
          See also: SAL 15:5, Sales, Motivating the Staff
        - 0:2-8.13 Pensions: Funding and Plans (Box 16)
        - 0:2-8.14 Performance Appraisal
          See also: SAL 10:5-3, Measuring Sales Performance
        - 0:2-8.15 Position Descriptions/Job Posting
          See also: SAL 35:1-3, Sales, Job Descriptions
        - 0-2-8.16 Recruitment; includes information on managerial/executive selection and headhunting
          See also: SAL 35, SALES RECRUITING, SELECTION AND TRAINING, particularly SAL 35:1, Sales, Recruiting/Selection
        - 0:2-8.17 Retirement
          See also: SAL 35:1-4, Sales, Retirement
        - 0:2-8.18 Suggestion Systems
        - 0:2-8.19 Temporary and Part-Time Workers
        - 0:2-8.20 Testing
          See also: SAL 35:1-1, Sales Aptitude/Psychological Testing
        - 0:2-8.21 Training and Development, N.E.C.
          See also: SAL 35:2, Sales Training and Development, and subsections
          - 0:2-8.21.1 Corporate Case Histories
          - 0:2-8.21.2 Action Learning/Training Techniques
            See also: ADM 0:2-8.21.9, Learning Process/Memory/Forgetting
          - 0:2-8.21.3 AMA (American Management Associations) Development Guides
          - 0:2-8.21.4 Assessment Centers
          - 0:2-8.21.5 Business Education, Undergraduate and Graduate; includes information on student attitudes towards business
          - 0:2-8.21.5 Business Education, Undergraduate and Graduate; includes information on student attitudes towards business (Box 17)
            See also: MKT 40:3, Marketing/Communications Careers, Education, Recruitment, Training and Development, all subsections
            - 0:2-8.21.5.1 International Business Education
          - 0:2-8.21.6 Career Advancement; pathing, mentoring
          - 0:2-8.21.7 International Training
            See also: Business Education, International Business Education and other ADM and IOP management subsections
          - 0:2-8.21.8 Job Rotation
          - 0:2-8.21.9 Learning Process/Memory/Forgetting
            See also: ADV 50:2-1.1, Memory for Advertising; ADM 0:27.2.12, Visual and Instructional Aids
            - 0:2-8.21.9.1 Programmed Instruction and Teaching Machines, includes video-based training
          - 0:2-8.21.10 Promotional Criteria
            See also: ADM 0:2-8.14, Performance Appraisal
          - 0:2-8.21.11 Sensitivity (T-Group) Training
          - 0:2-8.21.12 Skills Inventories
          - 0:2-8.21.13 Turnover, N.E.C., general information on why people leave jobs
            See also: ADV 50:5-4.15, Circulation: Turnover; SAL 15:5-6, Sales, Staff Turnover
            - 0:2-8.21.13.1 Relocation; includes information on executive mobility
            - 0:2-8.21.13.2 Resumes (Box 18)
            - 0:2-8.21.13.3 Termination
        - 0:2-8.22 Unionization, White Collar
      - 0:2-9 Planning, Corporate: The Concept, Principles, Organization and Implementation of and for Strategic Planning, N.E.C.
        See also: ADM 0:2-4.5, Economic and Business Forecasting; MKT 50:2-1.37, Technological Forecasting; MKT 50:2-4, Market Analysis and Sales Forecasting, N.E.C., and subsections
        - 0:2-9.1 Planning in Times of Unpredictability
          See also: ADV 0:3, Advertising in an Abnormal Economy, all subsections; MKT 45, MARKETING IN AN ABNORMAL ECONOMY
        - 0:2-9.2 Strategic Planning for the Smaller Firm
      - [Promotion Management--see: MKT 40:1-7, Sales Promotion Management]
      - 0:2-10 Public Affairs/Relations (Box 19)
        - 0:2-10.1 Public Relations, N.E.C.
        - 0:2-10.2 Public Relations...As a Marketing Tool
        - 0:2-10.3 Advertising as a Public Relations Tool
        - 0:2-10.4 Anniversaries, Corporate
          See also:ADM 0:2-10.7.1, Open House and Plant Tours
        - [Annual Meetings--see: Meetings, Annual
        - [Annual Reports--see: Reports, Annual]
        - [Brandstanding--see: ADM 0:2-10.22.1, Brandstanding]
        - 0:2-10.5 Budgeting for Public Relations
        - [Communications Audits--see: ADM 0:2-10.11, Evaluating/Measuring the Effectiveness of PR Programs]
        - 0:2-10.6 Communications, Organizational/Corporate, N.E.C.
          Includes information on internal communications. See also: ADM 0:2-7.2, Communications (Manager/Manager and Manager/Subordinate, Personal) Techniques, N.E.C. and all subsections
          - 0:2-10.6.1 Fortune series: Crosscurrents in Corporate Communications
        - 0:2-10.7 Community Relations (Development/Promotion), N.E.C.
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.4, Anniversaries; ADM 0:2-10.32, Social and Ethical Responsibilities, Corporate
          - 0:2-10.7.1 Open House and Plant Tours
          - 0:2-10.7.2 Plant Location
          - 0:2-10.7.2 Plant Location (Box 20)
            Includes information on: attracting industry; factors in corporate location decisions; plant site selection. This file should always be used with ADM 0:2-4.11, Migration of Industry: The Geography of Manufacturing, all subsections
          - 0:2-10.7.3 Inc.'s Report Card on the States; annual studies on small business climates
          - 0:2-10.7.4 Industrial Parks
          - 0:2-10.7.5 Site Selection Handbooks
        - [Company Histories--see: ADM 0:2-4.3, Business History, N.E.C.]
        - 0:2-10.8 Consumer Affairs Departments
        - 0:2-10.9 Copyrights
        - 0:2-10.10 Crisis Communications
        - 0:2-10.11 Evaluating/Measuring the Effectiveness of PR Programs (Communications Audits)
        - 0:2-10.12 Films: Business, PR and Sales
          See also: SAL 35:2, Sales Training and Development
        - 0:2-10.13 Financial Relations
          See also: Investor/Shareholder Relations
        - [Giving, Corporate--see: Philanthropy, Corporate]
        - 0:2-10.14 Grapevine Communications
        - 0:2-10.15 House Organs/Newsletters, Internal and External
        - 0:2-10.16 Image/Identity Building, Corporate (Box 21)
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.26, Name Changes, Corporate; ADM 0:2-10.21, Logos, Slogans, Trade Characters/Names and Marks, Corporate; ADV 50:4-3.9, Corporate Image Advertising
        - 0:2-10.17 Image/Identity Research
        - 0:2-10.18 Investor/Shareholder Relations
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.13, Financial Relations; ADM 0:2-10.24, Meetings, Annual; ADM 0:2-10.29, Reports, Annual
        - 0:2-10.19 Legislative/Government Relations (includes information on political activism)
        - 0:2-10.20 Libraries, Corporate
        - 0:2-10.21 Logos, Slogans, Trade Characters/Names and Marks
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.16, Image/Identity Building, Corporate; ADM 0:2-10.17, Image/Identity Research, Corporate
        - 0:2-10.22 Media Publicity/Press Releases, N.E.C.
          - 0:2-10.22.1 Brandstanding
            See also: ADV 50:4.3.8, Comparative/Comparison Copy; MKT 5:2-9, Positioning Concept; MKT 40:1-3.1.1, Branding
        - 0:2-10.23 Media Relations (meeting the press, media tours, etc.)
        - 0:2-10.24 Meetings, Annual
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.18, Investor/Shareholder Relations
        - 0:2-10.25 Meetings, Employee (includes information on bulletin boards)
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.6, Communications, Organizational/Corporate, N.E.C.; ADM 0:2-7.2.5, Conferences, Conventions, Seminars and Meetings, all subsections
        - 0:2-10.26 Name Changes, Corporate
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.16, Image/Identity Building, Corporate; ADM 0:210.21, Logos, Slogans, Trade Characters/Names and Marks
        - [Newsletters--see: ADM 0:2-10.15, House Organs/Newsletters, Internal and External]
        - 0:2-10.27 Patents and Patenting
        - 0:2-10.28 Philanthropy, Corporate, N.E.C. (Box 22)
          - 0:2-10.28.1 The Conference Board Annual Survey of Corporate Contributions
        - [Political Activism--see: ADM 0:2-10.19, Legislative/Government Relations]
        - [Press Releases--see: ADM 0:2-10.22, Media Publicity/Press Releases]
        - 0:2-10.29 Reports, Annual and Quarterly
        - 0:2-10.30 Research in Public Relations
        - 0:2-10.31 Selecting a PR Firm
        - [Slogans, Corporate--see: ADM 0:2-10.21, Logos, Slogans, Trade Characters/Names and Marks: Corporate]
        - 0:2-10.32 Social and Ethical Responsibilities, Corporate
          See also: ADV 25, DECEPTION, ETHICS, TRUTH AND TASTE IN ADVERTISING, all subsections; MKT 5:2-10, Social/Ethical Responsibility Concept; MKT 50:6, Ethics in Marketing Research
        - [Trade Characters/Names and Marks--see: ADM 0:2-10.21, Logos, Slogans, Trade Characters/Names and Marks]
      - 0:2-11 Risk Management
      - [Sales Management--see: SAL 10, SALES MANAGEMENT, all subsections; SAL 15, MANAGER/SALES FORCE RELATIONS, all subsections; check all references featured in these sections]
      - [Sales Promotion Management--see: MKT 40:1-7, Sales Promotion Management]
- Advertising Series (ADV), 23 Boxes
  - ADV 0. ADVERTISING'S ROLE, FUNCTIONS AND INFLUENCE
    - ADV 0:1 Advertising: What it Is, What it Does, N.E.C. (Box 23)
      Includes histories of advertising and information on functions, criticism, ethics, moral responsibilities, etc., when in combination. See also: ADV 0, all other subsections; ADV 25, RECEPTION, ETHICS, TRUTH AND TASTE IN ADVERTISING, miscellaneous subsections; MKT 5:2-8, Social/Ethical Responsibility Concept; MKT 35:3, Consumerism; ADM 0:2-10.32, Social and Ethical Responsibilities, Corporate
    - ADV 0:2 Advertising's Socio/Economic Influence, N.E.C.
      Analyses of advertising's benefits and detriments. See also: ADV 0:4-2, Industrial Advertising's Economic Influence; ADV 40, ADVERTISING RESEARCH, miscellaneous subsections
      - 0:2-1 No Advertising: Ideas of what it would be like if there was no advertising (for example, pieces such as Godley's How Much Does No Advertising Cost?
      - 0:2-2 Security Values and Advertising: The Financial Community's Stake in Advertising
        See also: ADV 50:4-3.15, Copy Approaches and Themes, Financial; ADV 40:2, Advertising Research, Proven Effectiveness, and subsections
    - ADV 0:3 Advertising in an Abnormal Economy N.E.C.
      see also: MKT 45, MARKETING IN AN ABNORMAL ECONOMY
      - 0:3-1 Advertising in a Recession Economy
      - 0:3-2 Advertising in a Sellers' Market (Box 24)
        - 0:3-2.1 Advertising in a Materials Shortage Economy
          See also: MKT 5:2-4, Demarketing Concept
      - 0:3-3 Advertising in a Defense (wartime) Economy
      - 0:3-4 Cyclical Behavior of Advertising
    - ADV 0:4 Industrial (Business Publication) Advertising: The Industrial Communications Process, N.E.C.
      See also: ADV 35:1, Business Papers, miscellaneous subsections; ADV 15:2. Business' Attitudes Towards Advertising; MKT 40:1-2.1.4, Advertising Management, Attitudes Towards Businesspapers; includes the DuPont Study
      - 0:4-1 Top Management's Involvement in the Industrial Communications Process: Selling Management on Industrial Advertising
      - 0:4-2 Industrial Advertising's Economic Influence
        See also: ADV 0:2, Advertising's Socio/Economic Influence, and all subsections
  - ADV 5. ADVERTISING AGENCIES
    - ADV 5:1 Advertising Agencies: What They Do; How They Do It (the agency business)
      - 5:1-1 Industrial Agencies (Box 25)
        See also: ADV 5:7, Agency/Media Relationships
    - ADV 5:2 Billings
      See also: IOP 10:2-6.1, International Advertising Agencies, Billings
      - 5:2-1 U.S. Agency Billings and Income (agency rankings)
      - ADV 5:2-2 Top Agency Billings by Medium
      - 5:2-3 Agency Business Paper Billings (top industrial agencies)
        - 5:2-3.1 Agency Business Paper Page Placement
    - ADV 5:3 Client Relationships
      - 5:3-1 Agency/Client Relationships, N.E.C.
      - 5:3-2 Agency/Client Agreements and Contracts
      - 5:3-3 Agency Performance Evaluation, Rating (agency audits)
      - 5:3-4 Agency Turnover (account switching)
    - ADV 5:4 Concepts and Controversies
      - 5:4-1 A la Carte vis-a-vis Full Service vis-a-vis Cartels vis-a-vis Boutiques vis-a-vis Buying Services, etc.
        See also: ADV 5:12-1, Agency Marketing Services
        - 5:4-1.1 Barter and Brokerage of Media Space and Time
          See also: MKT 5:2-1, Barter Trading Concept
      - 5:4-2 House Agencies
    - ADV 5:5 Financial Operations
      - 5:5-1 Agency Compensation: Fees vs. Commissions (includes information on liability)
      - 5:5-2 Cost of Operations (agency financial management) (Box 26)
        - 5:5-2.1 Price Waterhouse Guides to Accounting Controls
        - 5:5-2.2 Miscellaneous Costs such as Collateral, etc.
      - 5:5-3 Public Financing (going public, agency stocks and profits)
    - ADV 5:6 Legal Aspects
      See also: ADV 25, DECEPTION, ETHICS, TRUTH AND TASTE IN ADVERTISING, all subsections; ADV 30, LEGAL ASPECTS OF ADVERTISING; ADV 50:4, Copy, miscellaneous subsections; MKT 35, LEGAL ASPECTS OF MARKETING, all subsections
      - 5:6-1 Attorneys' Functions
      - 5:6-2 Mergers
    - ADV 5:7 Media Relationships
      See also: ADV 5:1-1, Industrial Agencies; SAL 5:5, Media Salespersons; ADV 50:5, Media Buying, Evaluation, Planning and Selection, all subsections especially ADV 5:5-10, Media Sponsored Research/Promotion, all subsections
    - ADV 5:8 Networks, Leagues, Associations, etc.
    - ADV 5:9 New Business Development (self-promotion; agency presentations)
    - ADV 5:10 Personnel
      See also: MKT 40:1, Marketing Functions, all subsections; MKT 40:3, Marketing/Communications Careers, Education, Recruitment, Training and Development, all subsections
      - 5:10-1 Agency Administration, General Concepts (people problems)
      - 5:10-2 Account Executives
      - 5:10-3 Creative Staff, N.E.C.
        See also: ADM 0:2-7.5, Creative Techniques and Creativity; MKT 60:1-1, Product Innovation, Development, Planning and Management, N.E.C.
      - 5:10-4 Executive Staff, N.E.C.
      - 5:10-5 Marketing Directors
      - 5:10-6 Media Staff: Buyers, Directors, Planners
        See also: ADV 5:12-3, Media Departments; ADV 50:5-5, Media Buying, Evaluation, Planning and Selection Factors, all subsections; MKT 40:1-2.1.5, Corporate Media Directors
      - 5:10-7 Recruitment, Training and Development
        See also: MKT 40:3, Marketing Careers, Education, Recruitment, Training and Development, all subsections; ADM 0:2-8.16, Recruitment; ADM 0:28.21, Training and Development, and all subsections; SAL 35, SALES RECRUITING, SELECTION AND TRAINING, all subsections
      - 5:10-8 Research Staff
        See also: ADV 5:12-6, Research Services/Departments; MKT 40:1-5, Market Research Management, and subsections; MKT 40:2-3, Market Research Departments
      - 5:10-9 Salaries
        See also: MKT 40:1-8, Marketing Communications Functions Compensation; ADM 0:2-8.4, Compensation: Executive/Management, all subsections; SAL 20, SALES COSTS, all subsections
      - 5:10-10 Technical Staff
      - 5:10-11 Turnover (people switching)
    - ADV 5:11 Selection
      See also: ADV 5:3, Client Relationships, all subsections
      - 5:11-1 Single vs. Multiple Agencies
    - ADV 5:12 Services and Departments
      See also: ADV 5:4-1, Concepts and Controversies, A la Carte vis-a-vis Full Service vis-a-vis Cartels, etc.
      - 5:12-1 Agency Marketing Services: What Should an Agency Offer? What Does a Client Want?
        See also: ADV 5:3, Client Relationships, miscellaneous subsections; ADV 35:3-2, Advertising Agencies and Direct Mail
      - 5:12-2 Film Departments
      - 5:12-3 Media Departments
        See also: ADV 5:10-6, Media Staff: Buyers, Directors, Planners
      - 5:12-4 Merchandising/Sales Promotion, Services/Departments
        See also: ADV 50:6, Merchandising, all subsections; SAL 30, SALES PROMOTION, miscellaneous subsections
      - 5:12-5 Public Relations, Services/Departments
        See also: ADM 0:2-10, Public Affairs/Relations, all subsections
      - 5:12-6 Research Services/Departments
        See also: ADV 5:10-8, Research Staff; MKT 40:1-5, Market Research Management, and subsections; MKT 40:2-3, Market Research Departments
        - 5:12-6.1 Libraries (Box 27)
          See also: ADM 0:2-10.20, Public Affairs/Relations, Libraries, Corporate
    - ADV 5:13 Starting a New Agency
  - ADV 10. ADVERTISING APPROPRIATIONS
    - ADV 10:1 Planning and Controlling Advertising Investments
      See also: MKT 40:1-2.1, Advertising Management
      - 10:1-1 Advertising Budgets: Preparation and Control, N.E.C.
        See also: IOP 10:3-1, International Advertising Management: Controlling the Overseas Advertising Operation
        - 10:1-1.1 Hendry Expenditure Analysis
      - 10:1-2 Allocating Budget Items (determining items that should or should not be charged to the advertising budget)
      - 10:1-3 Advertising Budgets as a Capital Investment: Commentary
      - 10:1-4 Long-Term Advertising Budgets: Proposals and Commentary
    - ADV 10:2 Presenting the Advertising Budget to Management
      - 10:2-1 Cutting the Budget and Overcoming Budget Cuts
    - ADV 10:3 Advertising Budget Analyses: Past and Future Predictions, N.E.C.
      See also: ADV 10:4, Percent of Sales Invested in Advertising, miscellaneous subsections
      - 10:3-1 The Gallagher Report: Annual Budget Survey
      - 10:3-2 Business Marketing: Annual Budget Survey
      - 10:3-3 Laboratory of Advertising Performance Surveys
      - 10:3-4 Discontinued Analyses (representative samplings to show methods of compilation)
        - 10:3-4.1 Advertising Agency Magazine
        - 10:3-4.2 ANA (Association of National Advertisers, Inc.)
        - 10:3-4.3 NIAA (National Industrial Advertisers Association, now B/PAA, Business/Professional Advertising Association)
        - 10:3-4.4 Printers' Ink
        - 10:3-4.5 Sales Management
        - 10:3-4.6 Tide
        - 10:3-4.7 Western Advertising
      - 10:3-5 ANA/MIT Advisor Project (and other commentaries on the problem of determining how much is spent for industrial advertising)
    - ADV 10:4 Percent of Sales Invested in Advertising (Box 28)